Wilton Historical Society Genealogy Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- Series 1. Family names
  - S - Z
    - Sanford family, undated (Box 5, Folder 612a)
    - Saunders family, undated (Box 5, Folder 612b)
    - Schenck family, undated (Box 5, Folder 612c)
    - Schilcher family, undated (Box 5, Folder 614a)
    - Schlichting family, undated (Box 5, Folder 612d)
    - Schmitt family, undated (Box 5, Folder 612e)
    - Scofield family, undated (Box 5, Folder 614b)
    - Scott family, undated (Box 5, Folder 613)
    - Scribner family, undated (Box 5, Folder 615)
    - Searles family, undated (Box 5, Folder 618)
    - Seeley family, undated; Covers the years 1793-1884. (Box 5, Folder 620)
    - Selleck family, undated (Box 5, Folder 622)
    - Seymour family, undated; File 623b includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. (Box 5, Folder 623a, 623b)
    - Sherman family, undated; Coverage begins from 1635. (Box 5, Folder 625)
    - Sherwood family, undated; Covers the years 1754-1865. (Box 5, Folder 630)
    - Shipman family, undated (Box 5, Folder 635)
    - Slawson / Slason / Slosson family, undated (Box 5, Folder 638)
    - Sloan family, undated (Box 5, Folder 639a)
    - Sloat family, undated (Box 5, Folder 639b)
    - Smith family, undated; Covers the years 1620-1942. (Box 5, Folder 640)
    - Smith, Eugene, undated; Covers the years 1839-1928. (Box 5, Folder 641)
    - Smith, Truman, undated; Includes Truman Smith's stationery. (Box 5, Folder 642)
    - Spencer family, undated (Box 5, Folder 643)
    - Squire family, undated; Includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's and G. Evans Hubbard's notes. (Box 5, Folder 645)
    - St. John family, undated; Covers the years circa 1590-1940. File 611a includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. (Box 5, Folder 610, 611a)
    - Sterling family, undated; Covers the years 1637-1947. (Box 5, Folder 650, 651)
    - Stetson family, undated; Includes David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. (Box 5, Folder 655)
    - Stewart family, undated; Covers the years 1662-1742. (Box 5, Folder 660)
    - Stivers family, undated (Box 5, Folder 662)
    - Stratton family, undated (Box 5, Folder 665)
    - Street family, undated (Box 5, Folder 667)
    - Stuart family, undated; Covers the years 1730-1855. (Box 5, Folder 670)
    - Sturges family, undated; File 682 and File 683 include David Hermon Van Hoosear's notes. See also GEN, Fitch. See also Sturges Genealogy Chart in MAPS 7-8. File 681 is also relevant to Sudlow family history. (Box 5, Folder 680, 681, 682, 683)
    - Sturges family - Maine branches, undated; See also GEN, Fitch. See also Sturges Genealogy Chart in Map Case Drawer 7-8. (Box 5, Folder 684)
    - Sturges, Helen Elizabeth Sturges - Diaries, 1915-1917; See also GEN, Fitch. See also Sturges Genealogy Chart in Map Case Drawer 7-8. (Box 5, Folder 685)
    - Sudlow family, undated; See also GEN, Sturges. (Box 5, Folder 687)
    - Taylor family, undated; Covers the years 1801-1958. (Box 5, Folder 700)
    - Terrill family, undated; Covers the years 1778-1974. (Box 5, Folder 710)
    - Thompson family, undated (Box 5, Folder 711)
    - Tito family, undated (Box 5, Folder 712)
    - Treadwell family, undated (Box 5, Folder 715)
    - Trowbridge family, undated; Covers the years 1636-1961. (Box 5, Folder 720)
    - Van Hoosear family, undated; Covers the years 1756-1952. See also GEN, Mendenhall. (Box 5, Folder 800)
    - Van Hoosear, David Hermon - Papers, undated; Details of his papers given to the library in 1993. (Box 5, Folder 802)
    - Van Horn / Van Horne family, undated (Box 5, Folder 810)
    - Wakeman family, undated; Covers the years 1638-1907. (Box 5, Folder 900)
    - Walker family, undated (Box 5, Folder 905)
- Series 2. Miscellaneous
  - Correspondence, undated; Contains requests for genealogical information. (Box 5, Folder 166d)
  - Genealogy, undated; Information on research procedures and resources. (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - Miscellaneous, undated; Notes on Wilton families by Doris Soldner. (Box 5, Folder 90)